<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid Tracker</string>

    <!-- Status -->
    <string name="status_no_contact_title">No Coronavirus Contact Detected</string>
    <string name="status_no_contact_description">We\'ll let you know if you\'ve come into contact
        with anyone, who has reported symptoms on their app.</string>
    <string name="status_symptoms_title">Please Self-Isolate</string>
    <string name="status_symptoms_body">You have reported symptoms within the past 14 days. Please
    self-isolate until the 14 days is over, to help save lives.</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_tracking">Enable contact tracking</string>
    <string name="enable_tracking_description">The app will remember everyone who you\'ve
        come into contact with (so long as they have the app). You can safely use other apps whilst
        this is running.
        \n
        \nYou may hear an occasional sound in the background - this is the app using ultrasound to
        detect nearby phones.</string>

    <!-- How it works -->
    <string name="how_it_works_title">How it Works</string>
    <string name="how_it_works_description">Covid Tracker keeps a list of everyone you\’ve come into
        contact with (less than 2m away), where they also have the app. Then, if one of these people
        reports symptoms, you’ll also be alerted to self-quarantine so that we can slow the spread
        together.
        \n
        \nEverything is anonymous, and no personal data (like your name) or GPS location data is ever
        recorded. Users will never be told where, when or by whom they have been infected.
        \n
        \nTechnically speaking, the app uses Bluetooth, Wifi and near-ultrasound audio for precise
        proximity detection. You may hear a very quiet sound every minute for 10 seconds - this is
        the near-ultrasound audio and we\'re working to make this even quieter.</string>

    <!-- Bottom Bar -->
    <string name="check_symptoms">Check Symptoms</string>
    <string name="report_test_results">Test Results</string>

    <!-- Symptoms Quiz -->
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_temperature_title">Do you have a high temperature?</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_temperature_body">This means you feel hot to touch
        on your chest or back (you do not need to measure your temperature).</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_cough_title">Do you have a new, continuous cough?</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_cough_body">This means coughing a lot for more
        than an hour, or 3 or more coughing episodes in 24 hours (if you usually have a cough, it
        may be worse than usual).</string>

    <string name="symptoms_quiz_negative_title">You are not showing the common symptoms of
        Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_negative_body">You may still be infected.\n\n
    Many people won\'t show symptoms for around 5 days, and others won\'t show symptoms at all.
    \n\n
    If you think you may have been infected, we still recommend that you self-quarantine to
    be safe.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_positive_title">You are showing symptoms of Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="symptoms_quiz_positive_body">Please self-quarantine immediately.</string>

    <!-- Generics -->
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
